(Penny:)Shut up!
(Leonard:)Sheldon, are you gonna join us?
(Sheldon:)Coming!
(Sheldon:)Greetings, friends.
(Leonard:)Greetings, whatever
the hell you are.
(Sheldon-bot:)I am a mobile
virtual presence device.
(Sheldon-bot:)Recent events
(Sheldon-bot:)have demonstrated to me
that my body is too fragile
(Sheldon-bot:)to endure the vicissitudes
of the world.
(Sheldon-bot:)Until such time as I am able
(Sheldon-bot:)to transfer my consciousness,
(Sheldon-bot:)I shall remain
in a secure location
(Sheldon-bot:)and interact with the world
in this manner.
(Howard(after Raj whispers to him):)Really? That's
your question--
(Howard(after Raj whispers to him):)when did he
put a ramp in?